Guide to the Woman's College records, 1928-1974 UA.25.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Office of the Dean.1928-1974
  - Alphabetical Subject Files, 1928-1974 [Dc60s; MGW38-70; OD25-70; OD25-72; OD30-71; OD43-63; OD45-72; OD45-72; OD62-72; OD63-71; ODc60s; ODMF63-73; ODMGW33-69]., 24 boxes
    - 25th Anniversary, Woman's College, 1955 (see also Dedications and Anniversaries, [25th Anniversary] and 25th Anniversary, Woman's College in Box 24, below) (Box 24)
    - Academic Advisory Committee, 1966-1970 [FERPA] (Box 24)
    - Academic Deans Meeting, 1968-1972 (see also the same title in the subseries Assistant to the Dean, below) (Box 24)
    - Academic Freedom, 1960s (Box 24)
    - Academic Guide for Freshmen, 1964-1967 (Box 24)
    - Academic Honor System, n.d; 1949-1959; 1964-1967 (see also Honors System, below) (Box 24)
    - Academic Standards, Committee on, 1951-1961 [FERPA] (Box 24)
    - Academic Standards, Cut System Study [Attendance], 1952-1958 (Box 24)
    - Accidents-Injuries (Employees), October 1963 (Box 24)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Learning Disorders Relating to the Study of Foreign Languages, 1970 (Box 24)
    - Administration Organization Chart, December 1, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Admissions, 1940-1972 (Box 24)
    - Admissions, Advisory Committee on Admissions to the Woman's College, 1954-1966 (Box 24)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid, University Committee on, 1964-1967 (Box 24)
    - Admissions, Early, 1963-1971 (Box 24)
    - Admissions, Reports from W.L. Brinkley, 1959-1960 (Box 24)
    - Advising Systems within the Woman's College, 1965-1966 (Box 24)
    - Affirmative Action Plan, March 24, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Afro-American Studies, 1968-1970 (see also Black Studies, below) (Box 24)
    - Alspaugh House, 1931-1953 (Box 24)
    - Alspaugh House, carbons, 1931-1953 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae, 1964-1972 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Association of the Woman's College, 1957-1972 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Association of the Woman's College, Long-Range Planning Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Coffee, 1951-1958 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Day, 1938-1972 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Newsletter, materials for first issue, 1964-1965 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Newsletter, second-fifth issues, 1964-1966 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Newsletter, sixth - ninth issues, 1967-1972 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae, Questionnaires, 1964-1967 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Room, East Duke Building, 1964; 1968 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Speeches, 1963-1969 (Box 24)
    - Alumni Affairs Department, 1950-1966 (Box 25)
    - Alumni Census, 1955 (Box 25)
    - Alumni Daughters, 1967-1972 (Box 25)
    - Alumni Loyalty Fund, 1954-1967 (Box 25)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1965-1972 (Box 25)
    - American Assembly, 1963-1966 (Box 25)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1955-1968 (Box 25)
    - American Association of University Women, 1964-1966; 1970 (Box 25)
    - American Council on Education (ACE), 1951; 1964-1966 (Box 25)
    - American Field Service, 1964-1966 (Box 25)
    - American Government Committee, 1964 (Box 25)
    - Anderson, Florence, [Carnegie Corporation], 1964-1965 (Box 25)
    - Angel Flight, 1969 (Box 25)
    - Angier B. Duke Scholarships, 1960-1972 (Box 25)
    - Anne Flexner Award, 1947-1963 (Box 25)
    - Art, Department of, 1964-1966 (Box 25)
    - Art, East Duke, 1966-1967 (see also Art, East Duke, 1966-1971 in the Dean of Freshmen subseries above) (Box 25)
    - Art, In-Houses, 1959-1971 (Box 25)
    - Arts and Crafts Workshop, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Arts Center, 1958-1969 (Box 25)
    - Arts Council, Duke University, 1951-1961 (Box 25)
    - Assemblies, 1932-1959; 1963-1964 (Box 25)
    - Assembly Rooms, Capacities, 1952-1969 (Box 25)
    - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1962-1972 (Box 25)
    - Association of American Colleges and Allied Groups, 1963-1971 (Box 25)
    - Association of College and University Housing Offices, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
    - Association of Women's Residences, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Attrition Statistics, 1949-1971 (Box 25)
    - Auditing, 1956-1968 (Box 25)
    - Auditorium, Alice M. Baldwin 1956-1968 (dedicated May 2, 1964) (Box 25)
    - Auditorium, Alice M. Baldwin, Projection Equipment, 1965-1966 (Box 25)
    - Automobiles, 1960-1971 (see also WSGA, Car Issue, below) (Box 25)
    - Aycock House, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Azalea Festival, Wilmington, 1949-1969 (Box 25)
    - Babysitting, 1962 (Box 26)
    - Band, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Bank, Central Carolina, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Barnes, Evelyn (see Alspaugh House, above and Scholarship, Evelyn Barnes, below) (Box 26)
    - Bassett House, 1939-1944; 1947-1948 (Box 26)
    - Beauty Pageants, 1957-1969 (see also Azalea Festival, Wilmington, above) (Box 26)
    - Bequests Committee, 1963 (Box 26)
    - "Bermuda Shorts" Proposal, 1960; 1964 (Box 26)
    - Bibliographies, n.d.; 1950-1964 (Box 26)
    - Bicycles, 1962-1972 (Box 26)
    - Bivins Loan Fund, 1928 (Box 26)
    - Black Students, 1965-1972 [FERPA] (Box 26)
    - Black Studies, 1971-1972 (see also Afro-American Studies, above) (Box 26)
    - Black Week, 1970 (Box 26)
    - Blue Jeans, [a service organization], 1968 (Box 26)
    - Blue Sheets (see Student Records, below) (Box 26)
    - Board Plan [Meal Plan], 1959-1972 (Box 26)
    - Board of Trustees, Reports to, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Board of Visitors for Woman's College, 1964-1971 (Box 26)
    - Bree, Dr. Germaine, 1963-1964 (see also Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life…" Correspondence, Bree, Dr. Germaine, 1962-1963, below) (Box 26)
    - Brown House, 1941-1944; 1947-1952 (Box 26)
    - Budget, Epworth Inn, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
    - Budget, General, 1964-1972 (Box 26)
    - Budget Material, advances, materials for residential staff, orientation, etc., 1969-1974 (Box 26)
    - Budget, Salaries, 1968-1974 (Box 26)
    - Budget, Wage-Hour Laws Affecting Residential Staff, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Budget, Woman's College needs and suggestions, 1962-1970 Busses, 1963-1971 (Box 26)
    - Calendar, Academic, 1962-1971 (Box 26)
    - Calendar, Residential, 1971-1972 (Box 26)
    - Campus Center, 1959-1968 (see also "Center" Committee and Dean's House, below) (Box 26)
    - Campus Chest, 1950-1964 (Box 26)
    - Campus Club, 1953-1970 (Box 26)
    - Campus Community Council, 24 hour visitation policies, 1968-1972 Card Keys, 1969-1973 (see also Key Control, below) (Box 26)
    - Carmichael, Katherine, UNC-Chapel Hill's Dean of Women, 1969-1970 (Box 26)
    - Carr Building Floor Plan, 1962 (Box 26)
    - Census, 1950; 1970 (Box 26)
    - Centennial, Duke University, 1939 (Box 26)
    - "Center" Committee (Woman's College Center), (see also Campus Center, above) 1961-1966 (Box 27)
    - Central Records Office, Committee on, 1951-1953 (Box 27)
    - Chanticleer, 1964-1965 (Box 27)
    - Chapel, Administrative Committee of the, 1966-1969 (Box 27)
    - Chaperones, 1963-1968 (Box 27)
    - Cheerleaders, 1956-1967 (Box 27)
    - Chemistry Laboratory, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Christmas Holidays, Reports, 1964-1967 (see also Student Activities, Student Christmas Dinner, below) (Box 27)
    - Chronicle, 1959-1970 (Box 27)
    - Church Board, n.d.; 1948 (Box 27)
    - Civil Defense, 1958; 1969 (Box 27)
    - Civil Rights, 1963-1967 (Box 27)
    - Class, Annual President's Report, 1942-1947; 1957-1958; 1961; 1964 (Box 27)
    - Class Attendance, 1962-1966 (Box 27)
    - Class Gifts, 1946-1967 (Box 27)
    - Class Honors, 1963-1966; 1970 (see also Honors Assembly, below) (Box 27)
    - Class Meetings, 1949-1960 (Box 27)
    - Class Night, 1959-1961 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1967 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1968 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1969 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1970 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1944, minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1945, minutes, 1941-1944 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1946, minutes, 1942 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1952, minutes, 1948-1952 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1941, Treasurer's register, 1937-1941 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1942, Treasurer's register, 1939-1942 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1943, Treasurer's register, 1939-1943 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1944, Treasurer's register, 1940-1944 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1945, Treasurer's register, 1941-1945 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1946, Treasurer's register, 1943-1946 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1947, Treasurer's register, 1943-1947 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1937, Treasurer's report, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1938, Treasurer's report, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1939, Treasurer's report and register, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1940, Treasurer's report and register, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
    - Class Scholars, 1963-1968 (see also Student Aid, Financial and Scholarships, below) (Box 27)
    - Co-Curricular Programs, 1966-1968 (Box 27)
    - Coffee House, 1966-1968 (Box 27)
    - Cole, Dr. R. Taylor, Provost, 1963-1968 (Box 27)
    - College Costs, 1966 (Box 27)
    - College Regulations, Judicial Code of Campus Living, 1963-1972 (Box 27)
    - Commencement, 1943-1974 (Box 28)
    - Commencement Committee, 1953-1969 (Box 28)
    - Committees within the Woman's College, n.d.; 1955; 1968-1969 (Box 28)
    - Community Council of the Woman's College (CCWC), 1966-1971 (was also known by the acronym CoCoWoCo until April 1970) (Box 28)
    - Computer Service, 1966-1967 (Box 28)
    - Conferences, 1964-1968 (Box 28)
    - Congress of Racial Equity (CORE), 1963-1964 (Box 28)
    - Constitutions, Charters of Campus Organizations, n.d., 1949-1972 (see also Associated Students of Duke University, above) (Box 28)
    - Constitutions, Classes 1967-1970 (Box 28)
    - Continuation Requirements, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Continuing Education for Women, 1964-1972 (see also Continuing Education for Women, Center for in Dean of Freshmen subseries, above) (Box 28)
    - Contraceptives and Abortion, 1964-1971 (Box 28)
    - Convocations, University Convocation Committee, 1962-1969 (Box 28)
    - Cooperative Program, Duke University and Consolidated University of North Carolina, 1963-1968 (Box 28)
    - Coordinate College, 1958-1970 (Box 28)
    - Coordinate College, Place of the Woman's College within Duke University, 1956-1969 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, Margaret Ball and Ellen Huckabee, 1955-1967 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, Mary Grace Wilson, Dean of Women, 1963-1972 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, President W.P. Few, 1925-1940 (Box 28)
    - Corridor Courses and Seminars, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Crafts Center, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Creative Arts, Student Efforts, 1964 (Box 28)
    - Curricular Requirement, 1970-1972 (Box 28)
    - Curriculum, 1951-1966; 1969-1970 (see also Danforth Workshop for Liberal Arts Education, below) (Box 28)
    - Alumni Affairs Department, 1950-1966 (Box 29)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1942-1962, continued (Box 29)
    - Danforth Foundation, 1962-1967 (Box 29)
    - Danforth Foundation, Teaching Fellowships, n.d. (Box 29)
    - Danforth Workshop for Liberal Arts Education, 1964 (see also Curriculum, above) (Box 29)
    - Day Care, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Dean of Arts and Sciences, Responsibilities of, 1967 (Box 29)
    - Dean of Woman's College, history and summary of duties, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Dean of the Woman's College, job survey, 1947 (Box 29)
    - Deans: Baldwin, Alice M., In Memoriam, 1960-1961 (see also Baldwin Auditorium, above) (Box 29)
    - Deans: Baldwin, Alice M., Retirement, 1947 (Box 29)
    - Deans: Baldwin, Alice M. "Those who make the wheels go round." A Salute to Dr. Alice Baldwin, 1965 [sound recording 10-inch inside start record and a 1/4- inch reel-to-reel audio tape duplicate] (Box 29, Audio-reel UA25.05.0006-RR-0001, Audio-phonodisc UA25.05.0006-PD-0001)
    - Deans: Ball, Margaret, 1962-1969 (Box 29)
    - Deans: Ball, Margaret, invitations and welcomes, 1963-1965 (Box 29)
    - Deans: Brinkley, Roberta F., 1960-1970 (Box 29)
    - Deans: Kreps, Juanita M., 1969-1971 (Box 29)
    - Dean's House, Use of as a Student Center, 1953-1966 (see also Campus Center, above) (Box 29)
    - Dean's List, 1954-1970 (Box 29)
    - Dean's Office, Organization and Duties of, 1927-1970 (Box 29)
    - Dean's Residence, Satterfield House, 1964-1972 (Box 29)
    - Dedications and Anniversaries, [25th Anniversary], 1954-1956 (see also 25th Anniversary, Woman's College, 1955 and 25th Anniversary, Woman's College in Box 47, below) (Box 29)
    - Dedications and Anniversaries, Dedication of Gilbert-Addoms, 1955-1957 (Box 29)
    - Dedications and Anniversaries, Dedication of the Woman's College Chapel, 1959 (Box 29)
    - Demonstrations [Civil Rights], 1964-1969 (Box 29)
    - Development Advisory Committee, 1965-1974 (see also the same title in the Committees series, above) (Box 29)
    - Dining Halls (see Board Plan, above) (Box 29)
    - Dinners, honorary, 1964-1969 (Box 29)
    - Directions for Educated Women (D.E.W.), (formerly Educated WomanPower Committee, EWP)1966-1971 (Box 29)
    - Disciplinary Committee, 1962-1970 (Box 29)
    - Divinity School, 1963-1965 (Box 29)
    - Doris Duke Foundation, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Dormitory Summer Newsletters, n.d.; 1956-1959 (Box 29)
    - Dorothy Thomas Room, Library East Campus, 1964-1965 (Box 29)
    - Drinking Regulations, 1942-1958; 1964 (Box 29)
    - Drugs, 1966-1971 (Box 29)
    - Drugs, Editorials on, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
    - Drugs, Governor's Conference, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Duke Endowment, 1964-1968 (Box 30)
    - Duke Forum, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Duke Planning Study, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Duke Players, 1966-1973 (Box 30)
    - Duke University National Council (see Alumni Affairs, above) (Box 30)
    - Duplication Office, Need for, 1966-1967 (mimeograph, Xerox, multilith) (Box 30)
    - ESSO Educational Foundation, 1965-1968 (Box 30)
    - Early Arrivals, 1970-1972 (Box 30)
    - East Campus Bell, "Ol' Marse Jack," 1958; 1964 (Box 30)
    - East Campus Store, 1966 (Box 30)
    - East Duke Building, Renovations, 1966-1974 (Box 30)
    - East Duke Chapel, 1947-1973 (Box 30)
    - East Duke Parlors (Use of), 1949-1963 (Box 30)
    - Edgemont Community Center, 1964-1965 (see also Living-Learning Experiments and Edgemont Community, below) (Box 30)
    - Education, Department of, 1963-1968 (Box 30)
    - Educational Administration, Committee on, 1962-1967 (Box 30)
    - Educational Goals Committee, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Educational Affairs Committee, 1964-1965 [FERPA] (Box 30)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, 1963-1969 (Box 30)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, Advisory Committee on West Campus Dormitories, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, Campus Landscape Subcommittee, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, College of Engineering Subcommittee, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, Committee on Auditoriums, Subcommittee, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, Woman's College Subcommittee, 1963-1964 (Box 30)
    - Emergency, Medical and Physical, 1963-1969; 1973 (Box 30)
    - Emerson, Alice, [consultant to Student Affairs], 1969-1971 (Box 30)
    - Employee Training Program, 1967-1968 (Box 30)
    - English Department, 1966 (see also English Department in the Academic Dean subseries, below) (Box 30)
    - Engineering, College of, 1963-1965 (Box 30)
    - Enrollment, 1956-1969 (Box 30)
    - Enrollment, increase, 1939-1959 (Box 30)
    - Enrollment, yearly, 1930-1956 (Box 30)
    - Erasmus Club, 1952; 1965-1967 (Box 30)
    - Examinations, schedules, etc., 1948-1966; 1970-1971 (Box 30)
    - Exchange Program - Free University Berlin, Germany, 1963-1965 (see also Study Abroad, Committee on, below; Exchange Program - Free University Berlin, Germany and Study Abroad, Committee on, in the Academic Dean subseries, below) (Box 30)
    - Exchange Students, [student government], 1960-1965 (Box 30)
    - Experiment in International Living, 1958 (Box 30)
    - Faculty, 1953-1972 (Box 30)
    - Faculty Advising System, Supervisory Committee for, 1964-1972 (see also Faculty Advisory Committee folder one, below) (Box 30)
    - Faculty Advisory System, 1952-1972 (Box 30)
    - Faculty Advisory System, handbook, 1953-1954 (Box 30)
    - [Faculty] Associates, 1964-1972 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Club, 1949-1967 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Daughters, 1951-1963 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Fellows Program, 1964 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Memos, 1945-1964 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Newsletter, 1964-1967 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Qualifications and Improvement, Committee on, "A Report on the Selection, Retention, Promotion, and Scholarly Productivity of the Faculty," 1962 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Salaries, statistics, 1930-1961 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Women, 1952-1965 (Box 31)
    - Fallout [Nuclear] Preparedness Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 31)
    - Fees, 1945-1960 (Box 31)
    - Fellowships for Interns in Educational Administration, 1971 (Box 31)
    - Female Visitation to the West Campus Dormitories, 1965 (Box 31)
    - "Fictitious Freshman," [collection of mailings received by entering freshmen], 1963 (Box 31)
    - Fifth Decade [Duke's 10 year plan], 1965 (Box 31)
    - Fifth Decade, Committee on Quality, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
    - Fifth Decade, Committee on Quality, Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
    - Fifth Decade, Enrollment and Dormitory Space, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
    - Financial Statement, 1964-1972 (Box 31)
    - Firearms, 1967-1971 (Box 31)
    - Flag Raising Ceremony, 1938-1964 (Box 31)
    - Founder's Day Exercises, 1954-1966 (Box 31)
    - Freshmen, 1970-1971 (Box 31)
    - Freshmen Advisory Council, 1961-1966 (Box 31)
    - Freshmen Statistics, 1957-1970 (Box 31)
    - Freshmen Tea, 1959-1966 (Box 31)
    - Fund Raising, 1964-1965 (Box 31)
    - General Motors Corporation, 1964-1967 (Box 32)
    - Geographical Distribution, 1962-1970 (see also Reports to the President in the Reports series, below, for annual geographic distribution listings) (Box 32)
    - German Department, 1964-1966 (Box 32)
    - Gilbert House, 1961; 1964 (Box 32)
    - Giles House, 1941-1944; 1947-1953 (Box 32)
    - Glamour Magazine, Profile Sketch of the Woman's College, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Glee Club, 1968-1970 (Box 32)
    - Graduate Fellowships, 1965-1967 (Box 32)
    - Graduate School, Statistics, 1962-1966 (Box 32)
    - Graduate Study Committee for the Undergraduate Colleges, 1964-1969 (Box 32)
    - Green Room, 1964-1972 (Box 32)
    - Grievance Procedure (see Proposed Structure of the Students' Concern, below) (Box 32)
    - Grievances, East Campus, 1971 (Box 32)
    - Guest Suite, Wilson House, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Gymnasium, 1967-1971 (Box 32)
    - Gynecology Clinic, 1969-1970 (Box 32)
    - Harrison, Evelyn, 1978 (Box 32)
    - Handbook, Woman's College, 1957-1968 (see also Student Handbooks, below) (Box 32)
    - Hanks, Nancy (Board of Trustees member), Correspondence, 1962-1969 (see also Development Advisory Committee, above and Development Advisory Committee in the Committees series, above) (Box 32)
    - Health Coordinating Committee, 1936-1954 (Box 32)
    - Health Services, 1964-1973 (Box 32)
    - Health Services, monthly reports, n.d., 1947-1970 (Box 32)
    - Hearing Committee, 1968 (see also Pickets and Protests, below) (Box 32)
    - Hispanic Research, Council on, 1963-1966 (Box 32)
    - History Department, 1963-1967 (Box 32)
    - Homecoming, 1964; 1967 (Box 32)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1963-1968 (Box 32)
    - Honor Code, 1947-1960 (see also North Carolina Association of Women Deans and Counselors, below) (Box 32)
    - Honors Assembly, 1963-1972 (Box 32)
    - Honors-Masters Program, 1962-1967 (Box 32)
    - Honors Program,[various colleges], 1950-1955 (Box 32)
    - Honor System, [various North Carolina colleges], 1956 (Box 32)
    - House Counselor Position, 1962 (Box 33)
    - House Counselor Study Group, 1957-1959 (Box 33)
    - House Counselors, Correspondence, Memos, etc., 1938-1971 (Box 33)
    - House Presidents, 1953-1955 (Box 33)
    - House President's Board, 1948; 1966 (Box 33)
    - Houses, Federation of 1969-1971 (Box 33)
    - Housing, 1965-1974 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Dormitory Information Misc., 1937-1970 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Dormitory Recommendations, 1938-1951 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Dormitory, specifications, 1955 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Duke-leased apartments, 1972 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Faculty Apartments, 1963-1966 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Gilbert-Addoms Residence Hall, 1954-1957 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Graduate Students, 1964-1966 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Open-Open Houses, 1965-1972 (Box 33)
    - Housing, Projected Dormitory Complex, 1951-1968 (Box 33)
    - Housing Statistics, 1962-1976 (Box 33)
    - Huckabee, Ellen Harris, Dean of Undergraduate Instruction, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Huestis, Charles B., [Vice-President for Business and Finance], 1967-1971 (Box 33)
    - Human Relations and Personal Adjustment, 1968-1969 (Box 33)
    - Identification Cards, 1963-1968 (Box 33)
    - Inauguration of Douglas M. Knight, 1963; 1966 (Box 33)
    - Inaugurations, 1963-1968 (Box 33)
    - Infirmary, 1949-1972 (Box 33)
    - [Infirmary], Dr. Dorothy E. Naumann, 1963-1969 (Box 33)
    - Infirmary, [Dr. Erma Smith], 1949 [RESTRICTED] (Box 33)
    - Infirmary, monthly reports (see Health Services, monthly reports, above) (Box 33)
    - Information/Regulations Bulletin, 1968-1973 (Box 33)
    - Information Services, Office of, 1963-1971 (Box 34)
    - Institutional Advancement, 1962-1969 (Box 34)
    - Insurance, 1963-1966 (Box 34)
    - Inter-Fraternity Council, 1960-1968 (Box 34)
    - Inter-Government Council, 1963-1967 (Box 34)
    - Integration, 1960-1966 [FERPA] (Box 34)
    - Integration, clippings, 1956-1963 (Box 34)
    - International Honors Program, 1965-1968 (Box 34)
    - International Relations, Committee on, 1963-1966 (Box 34)
    - International Relations Forum, 1963-1965 (Box 34)
    - International Students, 1947-1966 (Box 34)
    - International Students Advisory Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 34)
    - International Students Office, 1963-1965 (Box 34)
    - International Studies, Committee on, 1964-1966 (Box 34)
    - Internships, 1964-1968 (Box 34)
    - Invitations, n.d., 1961-1969 (Box 34)
    - Ivy, [academic honorary organization], 1956-1972 (Box 34)
    - Jarvis House, 1947-1948 (Box 34)
    - Job Analysis, of Woman's College Positions, 1961-1972 (Box 34)
    - Job Placements, 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - Joe College Day, 1955-1972 (Box 34)
    - Johnson's Wax Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - Joint Deans Meetings, [Undergraduate Schools and Colleges], meetings, 1960-1973 (Box 34)
    - Joint Staff Meetings, summary minutes, 1971 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Board, 1950-1963 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Board, Appeals Procedure, 1968-1969 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Board, Recommended Apartment Rule, 1966 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Board, Recommended Dorm Hours, 1966-1969 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Board, Statement on Procedure, 1965-1969 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Board, Woman's Student Government Association (WSGA), 1961-1967 (Box 34)
    - Judicial Procedures, 1966; 1968 (Box 34)
    - Junior Class Banquet, 1964-1967 (Box 34)
    - Judo, 1961-1966 (Box 34)
    - Juvenile Court, Co-Ordinating Council of, Durham, NC, 1935 (Box 34)
    - Key Control, 1970-1972 (see also Card Key, above) (Box 34)
    - Key Punch Machine Room, 1967-1968 (Box 34)
    - Laidlaw, Dr. Robert, [Sex and Marriage seminar and one-on-one conferences], 1964-1965 (Box 35)
    - Lane Bryant Award, 1964-1965 (Box 35)
    - Language Laboratory Facilities, 1959-1960 (Box 35)
    - Latin American Program (see Visiting Scholars in Residence, below) (Box 35)
    - Law, School of, 1963 (Box 35)
    - Learning Institute of North Carolina, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1969-1971 (Box 35)
    - [Letters re: Woman's College], 1963-1966 (Box 35)
    - Library Information, 1954-1972 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, 1970-1971 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, African Corridor, 1968-1969 (see also Contemporary Morality) (Box 35)